[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Do you know a person by the name of George Zimmerman?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "a", "person", "by", "the", "name", "of", "George", "Zimmerman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "And would you consider him a very good friend?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "consider", "him", "a", "very", "good", "friend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Best friend I've ever had.", "answer_tokens": ["Best", "friend", "I", "'ve", "ever", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "MD", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "In your opinion, calling somebody in reference to them as -- pardon my language -- (EXPLETIVE DELETED) punks?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "opinion", ",", "calling", "somebody", "in", "reference", "to", "them", "as", "--", "pardon", "my", "language", "--", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "punks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ":", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "That is ill will and spite.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "ill", "will", "and", "spite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "It is?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What is your overview of how today went?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "overview", "of", "how", "today", "went", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Are those consistent with striking somebody?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "those", "consistent", "with", "striking", "somebody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "The only injuries, as a matter of fact, you saw is the gunshot wound, two injuries on his knuckles, correct?", "question_tokens": ["The", "only", "injuries", ",", "as", "a", "matter", "of", "fact", ",", "you", "saw", "is", "the", "gunshot", "wound", ",", "two", "injuries", "on", "his", "knuckles", ",", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Any other injuries on Trayvon Martin at all?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "other", "injuries", "on", "Trayvon", "Martin", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Any bruising injury?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "bruising", "injury", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Any laceration injuries?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "laceration", "injuries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "You just put gun?", "question_tokens": ["You", "just", "put", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "And very quickly, Martin, what can we expect tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["And", "very", "quickly", ",", "Martin", ",", "what", "can", "we", "expect", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Tomorrow, I think we're probably going to hear from the person who actually did the autopsy.", "answer_tokens": ["Tomorrow", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "probably", "going", "to", "hear", "from", "the", "person", "who", "actually", "did", "the", "autopsy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, it's very, very difficult to assess this case, despite everybody's efforts to try and say it's not about race without bringing the race element into it, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Marc", "Lamont", "Hill", ",", "it", "'s", "very", ",", "very", "difficult", "to", "assess", "this", "case", ",", "despite", "everybody", "'s", "efforts", "to", "try", "and", "say", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "race", "without", "bringing", "the", "race", "element", "into", "it", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont Hill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "To suggest that he is a racial profiler?", "question_tokens": ["To", "suggest", "that", "he", "is", "a", "racial", "profiler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "You know, I think those are two different things.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "those", "are", "two", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "He's been called a suspect even through the attorneys in the courtroom?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "been", "called", "a", "suspect", "even", "through", "the", "attorneys", "in", "the", "courtroom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I think that he would have, Piers, and the reason that I say that is based on who George Zimmerman is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "would", "have", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "the", "reason", "that", "I", "say", "that", "is", "based", "on", "who", "George", "Zimmerman", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "-- for ignoring the advice he was given, getting out of the vehicle, following Trayvon Martin, and then getting into some altercation, pulling out a gun and killing him in cold blood?", "question_tokens": ["--", "for", "ignoring", "the", "advice", "he", "was", "given", ",", "getting", "out", "of", "the", "vehicle", ",", "following", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "and", "then", "getting", "into", "some", "altercation", ",", "pulling", "out", "a", "gun", "and", "killing", "him", "in", "cold", "blood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I'll tell you what.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Whether it's murder or not, doesn't there have to be some accountability?", "question_tokens": ["Whether", "it", "'s", "murder", "or", "not", ",", "does", "n't", "there", "have", "to", "be", "some", "accountability", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Piers, Piers, I'll show you why.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'ll", "show", "you", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Should he not have had a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "not", "have", "had", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Against police orders.", "answer_tokens": ["Against", "police", "orders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "-- that it was self-defense.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "that", "it", "was", "self-defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Really they're making a case?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "they", "'re", "making", "a", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "The fact of the matter, though, is -- well, let me finish -- let me -- let me finish the thought before you disagree with it.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "fact", "of", "the", "matter", ",", "though", ",", "is", "--", "well", ",", "let", "me", "finish", "--", "let", "me", "--", "let", "me", "finish", "the", "thought", "before", "you", "disagree", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "You want to talk about the law or morals?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "law", "or", "morals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What is your take on the Zimmerman-Trayvon court action we're seeing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "the", "Zimmerman-Trayvon", "court", "action", "we", "'re", "seeing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I think it's a race case without question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "race", "case", "without", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Well, how do I see it playing out?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "how", "do", "I", "see", "it", "playing", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "That proves murder?", "question_tokens": ["That", "proves", "murder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What about the possibility (INAUDIBLE) they could convict or a lesser charge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "the", "possibility", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "they", "could", "convict", "or", "a", "lesser", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, I think if a jury concluded that his so-called belief in the need to use deadly force was unreasonable, then, yes, so you get to manslaughter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "if", "a", "jury", "concluded", "that", "his", "so-called", "belief", "in", "the", "need", "to", "use", "deadly", "force", "was", "unreasonable", ",", "then", ",", "yes", ",", "so", "you", "get", "to", "manslaughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How much of an impact will that have potentially, as we saw in the O.J. case where many people believe there was a miscarriage of justice there, could we see a similar situation here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "an", "impact", "will", "that", "have", "potentially", ",", "as", "we", "saw", "in", "the", "O.J.", "case", "where", "many", "people", "believe", "there", "was", "a", "miscarriage", "of", "justice", "there", ",", "could", "we", "see", "a", "similar", "situation", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "It's hard to say, and I've actually given some thought to that issue.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "actually", "given", "some", "thought", "to", "that", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["O.J."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What are your thoughts on him today and what's happened to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "thoughts", "on", "him", "today", "and", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "When the trial ended and when I wrote a book about the trial called \"In Contempt,\" on the back cover I wrote this little thing, and I said that we all get ours in the end, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "the", "trial", "ended", "and", "when", "I", "wrote", "a", "book", "about", "the", "trial", "called", "``", "In", "Contempt", ",", "''", "on", "the", "back", "cover", "I", "wrote", "this", "little", "thing", ",", "and", "I", "said", "that", "we", "all", "get", "ours", "in", "the", "end", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "When you were in court today, what were you feelings?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "in", "court", "today", ",", "what", "were", "you", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, first of all, I was not in court today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "was", "not", "in", "court", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "I don't mean that in the sense of he's an innocent -- a guilty man made innocent, but will he get away with the fact that he did kill somebody without any punishment in the end?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "mean", "that", "in", "the", "sense", "of", "he", "'s", "an", "innocent", "--", "a", "guilty", "man", "made", "innocent", ",", "but", "will", "he", "get", "away", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "did", "kill", "somebody", "without", "any", "punishment", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Well, I don't know that, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Was that a mistake, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "a", "mistake", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "In my opinion, it was a horrendous mistake.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "opinion", ",", "it", "was", "a", "horrendous", "mistake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "How helpful or unhelpful was the testimony of Rachel Jeantel, Trayvon Martin's friend?", "question_tokens": ["How", "helpful", "or", "unhelpful", "was", "the", "testimony", "of", "Rachel", "Jeantel", ",", "Trayvon", "Martin", "'s", "friend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "You know, Piers, I've been asked that several times, the last several days.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "asked", "that", "several", "times", ",", "the", "last", "several", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["Rachel Jeantel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Have you had death threats, you and your family?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "death", "threats", ",", "you", "and", "your", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Of course, hundreds.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "hundreds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What is your reaction to the performance of that young black woman in a very difficult situation that she didn't really want to be in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "performance", "of", "that", "young", "black", "woman", "in", "a", "very", "difficult", "situation", "that", "she", "did", "n't", "really", "want", "to", "be", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "You know, I'm glad that you pointed out that this is a young woman who was in a difficult situation, that she didn't want to be in.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "glad", "that", "you", "pointed", "out", "that", "this", "is", "a", "young", "woman", "who", "was", "in", "a", "difficult", "situation", ",", "that", "she", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Oakland County Police Department"], "LOCATION": ["Pontiac"], "PERSON": ["Bobby Lee Taylor"]}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "You haven update, I think, for me on this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "haven", "update", ",", "I", "think", ",", "for", "me", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Yes, Piers, I'm really pleased to tell you that the Oakland County Police Department did in fact arrest and has now arraigned Bobby Lee Taylor, he was a 42-year-old Pontiac man.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "really", "pleased", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "the", "Oakland", "County", "Police", "Department", "did", "in", "fact", "arrest", "and", "has", "now", "arraigned", "Bobby", "Lee", "Taylor", ",", "he", "was", "a", "42-year-old", "Pontiac", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "How are you all coping collectively?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "all", "coping", "collectively", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Well, I'm glad you asked that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "glad", "you", "asked", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Granite Mountain Hotshot"]}, "docId": "130702pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "How would you like -- how would you like him most to be remembered, Claire?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "--", "how", "would", "you", "like", "him", "most", "to", "be", "remembered", ",", "Claire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I would like him most to be remembered as a hero, as a Granite Mountain Hotshot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "him", "most", "to", "be", "remembered", "as", "a", "hero", ",", "as", "a", "Granite", "Mountain", "Hotshot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire"]}}]